[
    {
        "question": "Can cats taste sweet things?",
        "answer": "No"
    },
    {
        "question": "Is a cat's brain more similar to a human's brain or a dog's brain?",
        "answer": "A human's brain"
    },
    {
        "question": "Are black cats considered lucky in Britain?",
        "answer": "Yes"
    },
    {
        "question": "How many teeth does an adult cat have?",
        "answer": "30 teeth"
    },
    {
        "question": "How many bones does a cat have?",
        "answer": "230 bones"
    },
    {
        "question": "Can cats survive falls over 65 feet?",
        "answer": "Yes"
    },
    {
        "question": "How many different sounds can cats make?",
        "answer": "100 different sounds"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the minimum temperature (in Fahrenheit) that indicates a cat might be sick?",
        "answer": "Below 100\u00b0F"
    },
    {
        "question": "How many toes do cats have on their front paws?",
        "answer": "5 toes"
    },
    {
        "question": "How many toes do cats have on their back paws?",
        "answer": "4 toes"
    },
    {
        "question": "How many kittens were in the largest known cat litter?",
        "answer": "19 kittens (15 survived)"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the maximum temperature (in Fahrenheit) that cats can tolerate with ample water?",
        "answer": "133\u00b0F"
    },
    {
        "question": "How many times per second does a cat's larynx open and close during purring?",
        "answer": "25 times per second"
    },
    {
        "question": "Is it safe to give cats milk?",
        "answer": "No"
    },
    {
        "question": "How many hairs per square inch do cats have?",
        "answer": "130,000 hairs"
    },
    {
        "question": "Can cats see color?",
        "answer": "Yes"
    },
    {
        "question": "How many times higher than its own height can a cat jump in a single bound?",
        "answer": "5 times"
    },
    {
        "question": "How many muscles control a cat's outer ear?",
        "answer": "32 muscles"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the average lifespan of a domestic cat in years?",
        "answer": "14 years"
    },
    {
        "question": "Are male cats more likely to be left-pawed?",
        "answer": "Yes"
    }
]